Marriage Completed
It's been a while, everyone. Once again, we
Enjoy Play! A playground for everyone! This is Gang Parade!
So, I would like to announce the results of the
Gang Parade, the Smile Manipulation Election, and I would like to announce the results!
We don't know yet!
We don't know anything yet either.
Thank you so much to everyone who voted today!
We have been tuning in every day, watching the progress, and voting.
We have been watching the progress of the contest and voting as well.
It was so exciting that we didn't have the results.
This time, the total number of votes cast was
12,326 votes!
Wow! Thank you so much!
There were so many people who voted, and the results are in.
Thank you all!
Now, let's unite!
First of all, let's see the ranking!
I'll start with 25th place and end with 1st place!
Let's do it!
Now, let's hear about the results of the Gang Parade Smile Manipulation Election!
Let's hear about the results of the Gang Parade Smile Manipulation Election!
No. 25, Tororoimera
24th place, The Music and the Game Premium
23rd place, Brand New Parade
22nd place, Cat Cop
21st, Runaway Parade
Ehhhhh...
Signal.
I know.
I mean the current final standings, the final, the final progress on the way to the final standings.
Oh~~
Let's continue.
Now, we're going to announce the 16th place.
In 20th place, Signal.
Signal.
No. 19, GT
No. 18, The Getaway Show
Ehhhhh...
No.17, Slide Rip
16th, Love Parade
Ohhh...
That's a little different.
This is pretty much all the music in one place.
There's a great Kin's part, isn't there?
No. 15, Important Song
Ehhhh...
There's Kundong.
Oh, no!
This one too?
Oh, no...
No. 14, Blood Compact
No. 13, Song of the Parade Runaway
Oh, no!
No. 15, Last Gang Parade
Oh, it's a parade!
11th place, Pow!
Amazing.
Nice try.
Oh, man.
This looks pretty different.
Oh, wow.
I have two of these.
Wow!
That's good. That's good. That's good.
Pow is an idiot.
Wow, Pau, that's amazing!
I'm so disappointed.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No. 10, 559 votes.
500?
It's mid-plastic.
3rd place
Third place.
I'm already all A's.
I'm all A's.
9th place
612 votes
I got about 6.
Breaking draw
Ninth place.
You're down.
6th place
Sixth place.
8th place
625 votes
5 votes
Billon and Zamande
Wow!
I can't cut it.
You're kidding me.
Hey, wait.
Beyon was big.
Beyonce on 9.
Made in.
That's it.
It wasn't a beyon.
Ew!
That's the tricky part.This is the carelessness.
I thought I could cut it at all.
I'm not careless.
This is carelessness.
Indeed.
It doesn't go all the way to victory.
Well, then, you can cut it from here.
From here.
Well, it's okay if you fall.
You can cut it from here.
There are a lot of people who can cut.
The ones we wanted to cut.
Let's start from here,
In this FC tour of ours,
I'm sure we'll cut them off at some point.
That's all.
Now, please come to No. 7.
Seventh place.
628 votes.
Power Parade.
Sixth place.
670 votes.
Challenger Limit Tower.
Good, good, good.
I'm happy.
I might be happy.
Fifth place.
709 votes.
Gang 2.
Here's how it's switched.
Yamambore has been born.
That's frustrating for Yaman.
Yaman has been born.
Fourth place.
797 votes.
Forest Art.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
I'm glad. I've been saying this since my debut, so I didn't.
You did it.
Because the members were together.
Because the members weren't together,
I want to see it so much.
I'm so excited!
I love to write songs,
I'm looking forward to seeing your songwriting.
I'm looking forward to seeing the ones we've done once, and then we'll bash them to shreds.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Third place.
830 votes.
Please listen.
Strong.
New outfit.
The only new costume.
First time wearing it.
Certainly.
For sure.
What kind of costume do you like?
This outfit.
More blue than red.
Second place.
Pfft.
Ugh.
Like I should make it for something a little bit.
hahaha
Overwhelming style.
Second place
1156 votes
Amazing!
Tearful stage
Oh!
Yay!
The life we fought for
Oh, my God!
Yay!
I'm so happy.
And
The First Annual Gampery Awards General Election
The opponents are
The 1st place
Total number of votes received
1235 votes
Wow!
That's great.
First place goes to
Gang Parade Flat Bending and Showing Busafire
Woohoo!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy I get to wear this again
That's great! I'm so happy!
So that's our 1st through 7th place costumes!
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Oh, my gosh, it's amazing. I got to wear it.
There's a lot of stuff in there that I wanted to get.
I got a lot more zombies. Zombies.
See you. You wore it.
I'll see what I can find if I can find it.
We'll be wearing these seven outfits for this summer's MC tour.
Thank you very much.
So, here we are, in first through seventh place...So, we have the 1st through 7th place winners this time.
But you still haven't decided which costumes to wear where and in which places.
But we still haven't decided which costumes will be worn where and where.
What will be the reason for this decision?
I'll tell you how we're going to decide.
I'd like to decide by moulette.
Yes!
It's a little bit gorgeous right off the bat, but you can't have it all!
This roulette shows the location of the live music club where we will be playing this time.
and the location of the live music club where we will be performing.
You can start from the first place...
Let's start from number one.
We'll decide in 7M.
Paines, right?
Yes, that's right.
Where will Paynes wear it?
Or go somewhere.
Do we go somewhere?
I asked for it.
Yay~
One, two, four, five, six, seven, eight.
What do we get? What do we get?
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Oh!
Oh, this is...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Looks strong.
I'm just barely out of Tokyo.
This is...
TEN763
Tokyo Zepdiver
Amazing!
That's amazing.
Isn't it great?
That's great.
That's amazing.
Oh, my God.
First place is awesome.
Tokyo.
I can wear it in Tokyo.
That's amazing.
First place.
Then I'll wear it in the semi-finals.
Semifinals.
Next...
Kamiatsu.
Six, five, six.
Here we are.
No kissing on the stage of tears.
Where is it?
Here we go.
Which way?
Closer, closer.
This circle, please.
Excuse me, sir.
Here we go.
Let's see what we get. What do you think?
It's early.
Shake your hand.
A little hand.
One more time.
Come on.
Come on!
Hit my dick.
I have to back it up.
I didn't know it was back already.
Come on.
Let's see what you got. What's going to come out?
What's coming out?
That was fast.
Next time I show you a creature...
Three.
What do we get? What do you think will come out?
Teletubbies, teletubbies, teletubbies, teletubbies.
Oh!
Oh...
Great.
What about you, Mr. Genta?
The Pink Steatistas made the stage.
Miyagi.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
The Final
Final
The final!
Amazing.
Great.
FINAL
FINALFINAL
Thank you
FINAL
The third place goes to.
I'd like to thank you for your support in the Preese's Liston Minor
It's a game of...
Is that a robot on the right?
New Costume
New clothes
yes
Yes, yes, yes.
Show me again and I'll give you the answer.
G-mover
Okay, then, the third place
Pleasent Minor.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Let's see what we got. What do you think?
Teletubbies, teletubbies, teletubbies, teletubbies.
What's that?
Huh?
All at once!
That's it.
All at once.
The very front.
All at once!
Okay.
Let's see what we get. What do you think will come out?
Teren-Ren-Ten-Ten-Ten
Oh!
You're off.
It's not good.
Really.
Really
Real pressure.
What do we get?
What do you think it's going to be?
Teren-ren, teren-ren, teren-ren, teren-ren.
Oh!
Oh, rent-a-cop
Renta
It's a big rental.
I'm going.
Okay.
Let's see what we can find. What do you think it's going to be?
Teru-ren-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten.
Yeah, yeah...
Yeah...
I can't do it.
Teren-ren, teren-ren, teren-ren.
Oh!
It's already gone.
This is hard
It's so hard
Se-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no
Ready!
Let's see what you got. What's coming out?
Teet, tet, tet, tet, tet, tet, tet, tet
Let's go!
It's the sea.
Seino!
What do you think will come out? What will come out?
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go...
Go, go, go!
It's out! It's out!
Is it good?
It's fine.
Read it out with your hands.
Te tete a te rellen.
I am now lay in this hand.
Now, we have decided on the costumes for the first through third place,
The girls are gathering in the second half.
I've already decided on the roulette, and I've increased the number of undecided places,
We have added two numbers each, so we will resume from there.
Next up would be the fourth place, Lincolnation.
The costumes for Lincolnation.
Seeeeeeeeee!
What do we get? What do you think it will be?
Te-te-te-te-te-te-ren
I love it!
Roulette power is good.
Here it comes! Fukuoka Drabble!
It's good. It's decided.
Drabrawl is decided.
Obihiro, Nagoya and Osaka?
Yes, that's right.
Now, fifth place. Gang Two.
Okay, next.
Let's go!
Now we are left with Obihiro, Nagoya, and Osaka.
Obihiro, Nagoya, and Osaka.
Would you like Osaka?
How do you want to go with Osaka?
I want to go to Osaka.
Let's go!
What do you think? What do you think?
Tet-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten!
But it looks good.But it's nice.
Nice.
Green.
Okay, one more time.
More than half.
Let's do it again. Let's do it again.
I'm a little too judgey.
Baby, I'm always half a judge.
Here we go!
Diamond!
In Nagoya.
Gang Two.
Yes!
So, that's the rest,
The rest is down to two more,
Obihiro and Osaka are left,
The costumes are the Hibiya Yaon costumes and the maid costumes of Awabarade,
and a maid costume from Awabarade.
So, we divided the 10 votes into 5 groups again,
So Yui is aiming for Osaka,
Go for it!
That's Yui, right?
I see.
Well, good luck, Yui!
Good luck!
Ready!
What do you think will come out? What do you think will come out?
Teren-ren, teren-ren, teren-ren
Wow!
Is this going to turn into a glue ball?
It's only the first throw.
Terellen-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten!
Wow! Oh no!
The pressure is rising.
What do you think will come out? What do you think it's going to be?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go!
Wow!
There it is!
It's Yui!
I'll do it then!
Yui looks good.
This outfit.
Yui too.
We practiced it earlier.
The opposite.
I like Yui!
You're a little bit too soft.
I don't want her to think that.
Then I want to entrust Osaka to you.
Here we go.
Ready, set, watch!
It feels good.
Here we go.
Ready!
Let's see what we can get. What do you think will come out?
Teren-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten.
What? Sorry.
I'm going to hold it again with two fingers.
Can I ask him to practice?
It feels too good to be funny.
Ready!
Let's see what you got. What do you think will come out?
Teletubbies! Teletubbies!
Ben!
It's over.
Do it twice more.
This one through the neck.
It's good, it's good, it's good. It's done.
Last chance, please.
Okay.
I'll do it one more time.
I've decided. Decide.
Ready!
What do you think? What do you think it'll be?
Teren-ten-ten-ten-ten.
Sorry.
Ah!
That was too fast!
I don't understand.
Why?
Stop acting like a dragonskip.
Dragon ship?
Why?
Why? Why?
I love it!
You can decide, you know.
I showed you.
This is the kind of character to pick up.
You dream of cartoons?
Only in my dreams!
Ready, set, go!
What do you think? What do you think will appear?
Teren-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten!
Bye-bye!Bye bye!
The end.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's the next sound. It's totally fine.
It's totally fine.
I said it before.
I really did.
Look who's here. Look who's here. Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Osaka!
Osaka, this is Number Hanzi!
That's great!
Amazing!
So, it's like a maid's beginning and ending with the Sendai Fix Yotis.
Isn't this amazing?
It's amazing. It starts with maids and ends with cleaning.
Indeed.
The beginning.
But it's amazing. I guess I feel completely different every day.
It's fun!
Oh my God!
It's going to be a heavenly palace.
We will be wearing these outfits for 7 shows in 7 different locations, so if you haven't purchased your tickets yet, please do so,
Please come and visit us. Please come and see us.
If you have a new marriage, you should definitely come.
You can only see it at this time?
We should close the door.
Please send me a letter.
It's the only time.
I'm sure of it.
We'll be waiting for you.
Since this is an FC tour, tickets can only be purchased by those who are members of the FC,
If you are not a member of the FC yet, I would recommend you to get a ticket.
If you are not a FC member yet, please find out where to get a ticket. So the costumes have been decided,
We had other projects, didn't we?
The one you predicted?
Yes, that's right. The Jan-Pre Derby.
We had fans decide the first, second, and third place winners, and so on,
I'm going to announce the results now.
What do you think? Who is confident?
I came in first place in the middle of the predictions.
That's great if you were first in the middle.
I think there might have been a lot of people who mentioned the name of the moon.
I think Coco also made an impression.
Because on Twitter, Coco Coating Coco was trending.
I guessed it, and everyone predicted the name of the moon, and I wondered why, but everyone predicted it.
Is that great? That's great.
I guess I'll start with No. 3 then.
Third place.
Three outfits.
Six outfits in the field.
That's great.
Six?
Six points.
Baby girl.
That's great.
I thought I was number one.
He thought he was number one. Baby Chan.
But if 10th place is DONBISHA, that one gets less points,
If you guessed the enemy's costume with less points, but you guessed Dombisha, you guessed 10th place.
That's it.
That's great.
Third place.
Third place?
Fifth?
No, I don't have one.
Okay, second place, please.
Second place.
Three costumes in the enemy.
Dombisha, right?
Dombisha 5th place among the enemy, Gang 2.
Miki Yamamachi.
7 points.
Yay!
You guessed 10th place.
I was surprised.
5th place?
Fifth?
That's amazing.
I'm surprised.
Yay!
What's next?
First place, please.
First place.
Four kinds of costumes among the enemies.
We have 2 types of Dombisha.
That's great.
The number of votes received is 11 points.
Next announcement.
Dream Celebration.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Where'd he go?
What was that?
That was second place.
Second place.
The Chinese took 6th place for dimensionality,
I had one left over.
Congratulations.Congratulations!
Congratulations.
That's great.
We'll all pay for our own expenses, this one.
You have earned a reward.
A reward for a dream celebration.
This song!
This is amazing!
That's amazing!
Isn't it great?
Not the yakiniku and kun.
Oh, my gosh!
Winner's comment
I didn't expect to win first place.
But you got two right.
That's great!
I was in...
Ganptwo and Linde Tensei.
Because he got two hits.
Tenkusu was number one.
Tenkusu and
Gyanpu Two and
Lynn got three.
Three targets.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
You've given me a wonderful reward.
I'll do my best now that you've given it to me.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's have fun together this summer!
I look forward to working with you!
Thank you very much to all of you wonderful people!
Congratulations!
And...
Yua's reward
has been decided.
I'm looking forward to it!
This costume contest
This is not all...
What is it?
I have a big announcement.
This costume contest.
You've made it public.
I'd like to thank all of you for coming to the party.
At the Gyanpa
We will hold a big exhibition of costumes
We are going to hold a costume exhibition in Tokyo.
Yay!
It's so nice!
We're going to have it made.
I'm sure the details will be coming out soon.
I'm sure the details will come out soon.
I'm sure we'll have more details soon, but I'm sure you'll be able to see the seven costumes
I'm sure we'll get more details soon, but I'm sure we'll be able to find the seven costumes
will be exhibited somewhere in Tokyo
will be on display somewhere in Tokyo.
I hope you will have a chance to see them
you will have a chance to see them directly
It's great!
Even if you can't come to Tokyo
you will have a chance to see it somewhere in Tokyo.
If you can't make it to Tokyo, you can still have a chance to see the show somewhere in Tokyo.
Please come and see us there too!
Please come and visit us!
Thank you very much!
So, for the next few weeks
It's been a few weeks
It's been a few weeks and about a month
The costume contest is now over.
We are looking forward to the summer
I hope to see you all on our FC tour
I think it will be a month where you can see us in various forms.
I think it will be a month for us.
I hope all of you who are members of our fan club
Please look forward to it!
That's all.
We
Enjoy Play, Everyone's Playground, Gank Parade.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to it!